{
    "subject": "resource/Slowdive",
    "predicate": "http://xmlns.com/foaf/0.1/name",
    "object": "Slowdive",
    "human_readable": "The name of Slowdive is Slowdive.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8314307928085327,
            "question": "Where are Slowdive from?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8286631107330322,
            "question": "Can you tell me about Slowdive?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.824551522731781,
            "question": "Who are the members of Slowdive?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8115885257720947,
            "question": "How would you describe Slowdive?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7892646193504333,
            "question": "When was Slowdive formed?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7614772915840149,
            "question": "What is the name of Slowdive's debut album?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7448009848594666,
            "question": "What genre of music is Slowdive known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7307384610176086,
            "question": "Is Slowdive the name of a musical group?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5240429639816284,
            "question": "Do you know any popular songs by Slowdive?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.028654539957642555,
            "question": "What is the name of the band?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The name of Slowdive is Slowdive.",
            "html": "dbpedia_4620_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Do you know any popular songs by Slowdive?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4620_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is Slowdive the name of a musical group?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4620_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What genre of music is Slowdive known for?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4620_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4620_103.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4620_22.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4620_31.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4620_41.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4620_48.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4620_59.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4620_63.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4620_66.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4620_74.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4620_88.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```"
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}